准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
章鱼哥罢工了
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
数数我的钱
Counting me money
钱比蜜糖还要甜
money sweeter than honey
钱钱这个
Money, money this
钱钱那个
Money, money that
利润养肥我钱包
Profit will make me wallet fat
什么
What
上个月利润降了三块钱
Profit's down $3 from last month
得加倍严格控制才行了
I've got to start running a tighter ship around here
感谢选择蟹堡王
Thank you for choosing the Krusty Krab
这是找你的零钱
Here's your change
章鱼哥先生
Mr. Squidward?
什么
What?
刚说的那堆找钱胡话是怎么回事
What's with all this change nonsense?
绕上去再绕下来
Over and under
抓住末端  穿过去
Grab the end, put it through here
往上绕过喇叭口
up and around, round the horn
系紧完工
bring it back home
海绵宝宝
Spongebob
付你工资不是雇你来玩扮装游戏的
I ain't paying you to play dress up
要呼吸到你休息时间吸去
Breathe on your own time
付你工资不是雇你来呼吸的
I don't pay you to breathe
你完全没付我们工资
You hardly pay us at all
我想起来了
That reminds me
有样东西要给你们
I got something for you
好啊
Yes
少得可怜的补偿
Our meagre restitution
发薪日甜美的香气
The sweet smell of payday
抱歉
Sorry
那是我准备干洗的衣服
That's me dry cleaning
这是你的票子
Here's your check
这是你的  海绵宝宝
and here's yours, Spongebob
你的钱我不能收下  蟹老板
I can't accept your money, Mr. Krabs
我热爱煎肉饼
Grilling is my passion
这什么东西
What is this?
账单
呼吸 说话 站立 存在
浪费时间 咀嚼
我就是站在收银台都得付钱给你
You're making me pay you to stand at the cash register?
你这什么意思
What is the meaning of this?
你发什么神经
Have you gone off the deep end?
这里得做出一点改变
There's going to be a few changes around here
只要每次逮到你们两个在偷懒
Every time I catch you two goofing off
我就要罚你们钱
I'm going to charge you for it
还有20
and 20
拿去吧  蟹老板
Here you go, Mr. K
这么多钱应该够缴清我的冒失行为了
I think this should cover all my nonsense
再给五毛钱
And here's an extra 50 cents
作为我还系了鞋带的罚款
for when I was tying my shoe
海绵宝宝  你这是在干什么
Spongebob, what do you think you're doing?
我只是在缴清我欠蟹老板的钱
I'm just giving Mr. Krabs the money I owe him
我一分钱都不给那个小气螃蟹
Well I am not paying that cheapskate Krabs one cent
建议你也照着我做
And I suggest you do the same
为什么
Why?
我们工人必须联合起来
We've got to unite as workers
要求老板给予我们应得的尊重
and demand the respect we deserve from the boss
其实  我跟你应该罢工
In fact, you and I should go on strike
我跟你要罢工
You and me go on strike?
对
Sure
毕竟你也很喜欢你的工作  对吧
After all you like your job, right?
对
Right
你想一直在这工作下去  对吧
And you want to keep working here, right?
对
Right
而且工作期间
And while you work here
还希望得到公正对待  对吧
you expect to be treated fairly, right?
对
Right
那就一起来罢工
Then let's go on strike
罢工
A strike
我们要罢工了
We're going on strike
虽然不知道罢工什么意思
I still don't know what strike means
但我们要罢工了
But we're going on a strike
你猜怎么着  蟹老板
Guess what, Mr. Krabs
我跟章鱼哥要罢工了
Me and Squidward are going to go on strike
罢工
A strike?
对
Yeah
你意思是说你们要做抗议标语牌吗
You mean you're going to make picket signs?
对
Yeah
还要做抗议演讲
And you're going to make protest speeches?
对  对
Yeah, yeah
而且还要求我得尊重你们
And you're going to demand me respect?
对
Yeah
不  不
No-no
章鱼哥  你不早说我会被开除
Squidward, you didn't tell me I was going to get fired
没有蟹堡王了
Without the Krusty Krab--
我
I--
章鱼哥
Squidward
你能抱抱我吗
Could you hold me?
我感觉不舒服
I think I'm going be sick
海绵宝宝
Spongebob
告诉你个消息  海绵宝宝
Newsflash, Spongebob
我也被开除了
I got fired too
所以我们才要罢工
This is exactly why we need to go on strike
他再也不能这么对待我们了
He can't treat us like this anymore
他还欠我们一切无法挽回的珍贵时光
He owes us for all the precious irretrievable moments
浪费进了这个垃圾堆里的时光
we've wasted in this trash heap
不久他就会发现
Soon he'll realise
招聘
他需要我们  胜过我们需要他
he needs us more than we need him
我们是团结的工人
We are workers united
抱歉
Sorry
照着我说的做  海绵宝宝
Just do exactly as I say, Spongebob
不久之后
and in no time
你不仅能重新上岗  还能获得更多
you will have your job back, and more
获得更多
And more?
好了海绵宝宝  听好
All right Spongebob, now listen up
我要教你罢工
I'm going to have to teach you how to strike
首先  先扔掉我们的制服
First, we must get rid of our uniforms
那是压迫的象征
They are a symbol of our oppression
我要你把你帽子扔到地上去
I want you to throw your hat on the ground
就这样
like so
现在踩个稀巴烂
Now, stomp it into the dust
到你了  海绵宝宝
Your turn, Spongebob
这就对了
That's the idea
快扔到地上去
Now throw it on the ground
我做不到  章鱼哥
I can't do it, Squidward
这顶帽子是我朋友
This hat is my friend
从来没压迫过我
It never oppressed me
海绵宝宝  你太可悲了
Spongebob, you're pathetic
你看
Look
我把帽子扔到地上了
I threw my hat on the ground
不打自招
A confession
下次三思而扔垃圾
Next time think before you litter
好
OK
海绵宝宝注意听
Pay attention Spongebob
我们现在要做抗议标语牌
Now we're going to make picket signs
这是罢工最重要的一部分
This is a very important part of striking
这样行吗  章鱼哥
Like this, Squidward?
不是栅栏  白痴
Not A picket fence, you ding-dong
是标语牌
Picket sign
抠 鼻
这样呢
How's this?
不行
No
这才是抗议标语牌
This is a picket sign
蟹堡王不公正
Krusty Krab Unfair
短小精悍  直击重点
Short, sweet and to the point
这样呢  章鱼哥
How about this, Squidward?
蟹堡王狂欢会
海绵宝宝  是不公正
Spongebob, it's unfair
不是狂欢会
not fun fair
狂欢会
A fun fair?
在哪
Where?
我很想去狂欢
I could go for some fun
就在蟹堡王
At the Krusty Krab
大家听我说
Hey everybody
一起去狂欢会狂欢吧
Let's go to the fun fair
不公正的蟹堡王
Krusty Krab is unfair
不公正
里面藏着蟹老板
Mr. Krabs is in there
小破店里无情站
Standing at the concession
密谋压迫不一般
plotting his oppression
那什么意思
What the heck does that mean?
不知道
I don't know
章鱼哥要我对大家喊的
Squidward told me to yell it at people
那你一定就是海绵宝宝了
Then you must be Spongebob Squarepants
对
Yes
兄弟  你就是厨师界的传奇
Dude, you are like a fry cook legend
能在我锅铲上面签名吗
Will you sign my spatula?
能给有志气的厨师做什么都行
Anything for an aspiring fry cook
请问你是来帮忙罢工的吗
So, did you come down to help out the cause?
不
No
我是来抢你饭碗的
I came to take your job
谢谢兄弟
Thanks dude
请注意  海绵宝宝
Attention Spongebob
你罢工水平太烂了
You are a terrible striker
你让你的继任者
You just let your replacement
越过了我们罢工的铜墙铁壁
cross our picket line
完全没有要挟他
without so much as a single threat
对不起  章鱼哥
I'm sorry, Squidward
要不我再试试标语牌法
How about I try the signs again?
我爱
蟹堡王
别管标语牌了
Forget the signs
我有事要让你做
I got something for you to do
站到那边去
Go stand over there
这样吗  章鱼哥
Like this, Squidward?
快到了
Almost
再往右边一点  完美
A little more to the right, and perfect
裤头村的居民们  请注意
Attention people of Bikini Bottom
你们大家都被欺骗了
You have been cheated and lied to
我就知道
I knew it
温和的劳动者再也不能
The gentle labourer shall no longer
遭到蟹老板贪财黑心的大肆伤害
suffer from the noxious greed of Mr. Krabs
那家伙在说什么
What's that guy talking about?
不知道
I don't know
不过他手上有个喇叭
But he's got a megaphone
我们要拆开压迫的木板
We will dismantle oppression board by board
把大企业的根基锯成两半
We'll saw the foundation of big business in half
即便需要一辈子
even if it takes an eternity
我不知道章鱼哥是在说什么
Gee, I don't know what Squidward's talking about
不过感觉挺有道理
But he sure sounds convincing
有了你的支持
With your support
我们会让人民意志的铁锤
we will send the hammer of the people's will
砸穿蟹老板奴役之家的窗户
crashing through the windows
of Mr. Krabs' house of servitude
支持这么久都让我饿坏了
All this supporting is making me hungry
大家去买蟹黄堡来吃吧
Hey everybody, let's go get a Krabby patty
没人在乎劳动者的命运
Nobody gives a care about the fate of labour
能立刻得到满足就让他们全跑了
as long as they can get their instant gratification
讲得真好  章鱼哥
That was a great speech, Squidward
你都快让大家全听你的了
You practically had them eating out of your hands
然而并没有  对吧章鱼哥先生
But they didn't, did they, Mr. Squidward?
那群看客都忙着听我的了
Because they were too busy eating out of mine
真希望你们两个能早点罢工
I wish you two would had gone on strike earlier
谢谢你吸引顾客来花钱
Thanks for attracting all these paying customers
拿标牌加喊口号可太能引流了
with all your signage and your sloganeering
好了  蟹老板
All right, Mr. Krabs
你这次太过分了
You've gone too far this time
虽然你可以欺辱我
You can pick on me
但章鱼哥是伟大领袖
but Squidward is a great leader
我们是团结的工人
We are workers united
我们已经受够了你的贪财黑心
We're tired of your smelly greed
我们要锯开你的桌子
And we're going to saw your tables
用人民的铁锤砸烂东西
and we're going to smash stuff with the people's hammer
我们要
And we're going to--
We're going to--
章鱼哥  另外那段是什么
Squidward, what was that other part?
我们要拆开你的压迫
Dismantle your oppressive establishment?
对
Yeah
那个也是
That too
我跟章鱼哥要一直罢工下去
And me and Squidward are going to stay on strike
没收到应得的  就绝不罢休
until we get what we deserve
即便得罢工到永远
Even if it takes forever
永远
Forever
跟海绵宝宝罢工到永远
On strike with Spongebob forever
蟹堡王
还是不公正
章鱼哥  蟹老头肯定
Hey Squidward, I bet old man Krabs
会在将来某天破产
is going to break any day
章鱼哥
Squidward?
对吧  章鱼哥
Yeah, Squidward?
得去求蟹老板要回原先的工作
I've got to beg Mr. Krabs for my job back
了结这场噩梦
and put an end to this nightmare
晚上好  章鱼哥先生
Evening, Mr. Squidward
我刚路过这附近
I was just in the neighbourhood
然后我
And I uh--
就想顺道过来求你回来上班
thought I'd drop by to beg you to come back to work
蟹堡王就快垮了
The Krusty Krab is a wreck
没有你和那个黄色小子  我快完蛋了
I'm ruined without you and then that little yellow guy
我雇的青少年把蟹堡王快搞垮了
The teenagers I hired is ruining the place
最糟糕的就是
And the worst part is--
他们就是缠着我不放
they won't leave me alone
好棒  蟹老板
All right, Mr. Krabs
懂我意思了吧
See what I mean
章鱼哥  拜托你回来吧
Squidward, please you gotta come back
我们想要的你都会给吗
You'll give us anything we want?
对  都会
Yes, anything
意下如何  章鱼哥先生
So what do you say, Mr. Squidward?
你的遭遇让我心如刀绞  蟹老板
Your story breaks my heart, Mr. Krabs
不然我们就散散步  一起
Why don't we take a little walk and uh--
讨论我的条件
discuss my terms
我的钱包有种不祥的预感
I got a bad feeling in the pit of me wallet
万恶的黑心老板
Hey, mean Mr. Bossman
罢工
这工作我再也不干
I'm quitting this here job
跟章鱼哥罢工真是太兴奋了
Gee, being on strike with Squidward sure is a kick
章鱼哥的话语依然在我耳边萦绕着
Squidward's words are still buzzing around in my head
宛如愤怒水母在飞舞
like an angry jellyfish
章鱼哥说得对
Squidward was right
我不能光坐这儿不动
I can't just sit here
要来行动了
It's time for action
我要恢复劳动人民应有的荣耀
I will restore the working man to his rightful glory
我要拆开这蟹堡王压迫的木板
I will dismantle
this oppressive establishment board by board
我要把这专制的桌子锯成两半
I will saw the tables of tyranny in half
咀嚼大企业的脚踝
Gnaw at the ankles of big business
章鱼哥会特别骄傲的
Squidward will be so proud
章鱼哥  谈判可真是激烈
Well Squidward, those were intense negotiations
很高兴你能换位思考  蟹老板
I'm glad you saw it our way, Mr. Krabs
现在我能开除那群青少年
Now I can fire them teenagers
把我的两位好小子召回来了
and get me two golden boys back
上班时间见
Well, see you at work
海绵
Sponge--
海绵宝宝  你都干了什么好事
Spongebob, what have you done
我完完全全照你说的做了  章鱼哥
I did exactly as you said, Squidward
我拆了蟹堡王
I dismantled the establishment
现在工作肯定能要回来了
Now we'll get our jobs back for sure
章鱼哥
Squidward
海绵宝宝
Spongebob
什么事  蟹老板
Yes, Mr. Krabs?
要来了
Here it comes
为了赔偿这些损失
In order to pay off these damages
你们两个要为我工作  一辈子
you two are going to work for me forever
罢工成功了  章鱼哥
The strike worked Squidward
我们的工作回来了
We got our jobs back
永远
Forever
一辈子后
海绵宝宝
珊迪和虫子
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜总监
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
啊  裤头村又一个祥和的夜晚
Ah, another peaceful evening in Bikini Bottom
聆听这一热带海域的寂静
Listen to the tropical tranquility
裤头村
请来两大勺
Two scoops, please
谢谢
Thank you
零钱不用找了
You keep the change
什么
What?
蟹堡王
我看到了
I saw it
特别大
It was big
扭来扭去
It was all wiggly
把东西全吃了
And it ate everything
太可怕了
That's horrible
那是一只阿拉斯加牛虫
It was an Alaskan Bull Worm
阿拉斯加
牛
虫
它吃了我的独轮车
He ate my wheelbarrow
它吃了我家小孩的作业
He ate my children's homework
都这样了还有必要说吗
Do I need to say it?
怎么办才能自保
How can we protect ourselves?
有了
I've got it
买个蟹黄堡吧
Let's all buy a Krabby patty
应该要把大门锁紧
We should lock our doors
应该要打电话找我外甥
We should call my nephew
应该要挖护城河
We should dig a mote
应该要带走裤头村
We should take Bikini Bottom
推到别处去
and push it somewhere else
那办法可能太疯狂了
That idea may just be crazy enough--
狂得能害死大家
to get us all killed
找个谁去追踪它
Let's get someone to go after it
没有谁会傻到
There ain't no one fool enough
去对付阿拉斯加牛虫
to take on an Alaskan bull worm
这边有厕所吗
You got a bathroom in this place?
在后面
In the back
谢谢
Thanks
我可以帮你们抓虫
I'll get your worm for ya
前提是愿意提供报酬
that is if you're willing to pay
不行
No
你一分钱也休想找我要
You'll never get a cent out of me
休想
Never
我宁愿那条虫马上就进来
I'd rather that worm come in here right now
生吃了你们大家
and eat you all alive
抱歉
Sorry
讨厌啦
Aw shucks
我才不要你的钱
I don't want your money
单纯渲染一下气氛而已
I was just playing up the drama of the moment is all
没错
Nope
我之所以要平白无故解决掉那条虫
I'm gonna take that spineless critter down for nothing
是因为这是私人恩怨
Because this is personal
看  我尾巴不见了
Look, my tail's gone
那害虫一定在我背后偷袭了  胆小鬼
Varmit must have got it
while I had my back turned, the coward
我要夺回属于我的东西
I am gonna get back what's mine
什么
What
可是珊迪  你不知道你的对手是什么
But Sandy, you don't know what you're up against
我们说的可是阿拉斯加牛虫
We are talking about an alaskan bull worm
阿拉斯加
牛
虫
虽然我不了解阿拉斯加
Well I don't know nothing about Alaska
但是你看
but lookie here
在我德克萨斯老家  我套过牛
Back in Texas, I wrangled bulls
也套过虫
and I wrangled worms
在我看来
As far as I'm concerned
牛和虫一起套完全就是省了一条绳
doing them both together just saves rope
现在我要去把虫子打得落花流水了
Now I'm gonna go kick me some worm tail
可是珊迪  你不知道
But Sandy, you don't know
放心好了  海绵宝宝
Don't worry, Spongebob
不会耗太久的
I won't be long
珊迪
Sandy
快去抓它  珊迪
Go get him Sandy
我们对你信心满满
We have the utmost confidence in you
刚刚你想到了什么办法
Now what was that idea of yours?
推
Push
等等
Wait
珊迪
Sandy
海绵宝宝  是要来看戏吗
Hey Spongebob, you coming to watch?
珊迪
Sandy
别去
Don't go
为什么
Why not?
珊迪  我看到了
Sandy I saw it
它又大又可怕
It's big, scary
大
可怕
粉红
还粉红
and pink
派大星的肚脐眼也这样
So's Patrick's belly button
那玩意我也不怕
But I ain't afraid of that neither
它会把你打败的
You'll get massacred
海绵宝宝  我可是德克萨斯松鼠
Spongebob, I'm from Texas
你眼中的大  跟我眼中的大
What you think is big and what I think is big
根本是两种完全不同的大
are two totally different bigs
并且它抢了我的尾巴
Besides, he's got my tail
绝对不能坐视不管
I can't take that sitting down
好
OK
可是
But--
万一抢你尾巴的不是那条虫呢
what if the worm didn't take your tail?
要是抢我尾巴的不是虫  那是谁干的
If that worm ain't got my tail, who does?
是我
I do
你吗
You do?
在哪
Where?
我口袋里
In my pocket
那你怎么不早说
Well why didn't you just say so?
快拿来
Give it here
快啊
Come on
海绵宝宝  那是一根回形针
Spongebob, that's a paperclip
还有一条线头
and a piece of string
才不是
No it's not
就是你的尾巴
This is your tail
海绵宝宝
Spongebob
你凭什么知道那不是
How would you know?
尾巴在后面根本看不到
It's always behind you
别去
Don't go
海绵宝宝  你有什么毛病
Spongebob, what is the matter with you?
我要去给那条没腿的坏蛋来点教训
Now I'm gonna go give that legless rascal what for
不管你说什么都阻止不了我
And there ain't nothing you can say to stop me
是吗  那我就说
Oh yeah, what if I said
板腊根付地甭侬吸
Blaggenfidibblenohip
不得不承认  确实拖了我一点时间
Well, I gotta admit that's slowing me down
但我还是要去找它
But I'm still going for him
尾巴也没大家说得那么值
You know, tails are so overrated
别想尾巴的事情了  回去吧
Let's just forget about it and go home
我有果仁冰淇淋
I've got ice cream with nuts
珊迪  我是你爹
Sandy, this is your Pappy speaking
我要禁止你去追踪这条虫
and I forbid you to go after this worm
你给我回来  大小姐
Y'all come back here, young lady
你又不是我爹
You ain't my pa
珊迪  要想去找虫
Sandy, if you want to get to that worm
必须先过我这关
you're going to have to go through me
珊迪  不行
Sandy, no
我不能让你走
I can let you
我不能让你没命
I'm not going to let you get killed
你要是真找到了  它肯定会吃掉你
If you find him you'll get eaten for sure
某些海里的笨虫子绝对不可能
Ain't no way some dumb old sea worm
会吃掉我
is going to make a meal a me
我德克萨斯来的  可强了
I am too Texas tough
不行
No-no
你还不够强
not tough enough
Not tough enough
海绵宝宝  别瞎操心了
Spongebob, quit your worrying
我能管好我自己的
I can take care of myself
毕竟谁是裤头村最强壮的生物
After all, who's the strongest critter in Bikini Bottom?
是你
You are
是谁最会
And who put the
打空手道
K in Karate?
是你
You did
是谁常常保住了你的黄屁股
And who saves your yellow backside
每次都不让它摔坏
from certain destruction on a regular basis?
珊迪所有
是你
You do
对
Right
我也能应付得来你的小小牛虫
And I can handle your little bull worm too
因为我最强
Cause I am the best there is
根本没东西
There ain't nothing
能又大又凶到我抓不住的地步
too big or too ornery for me to catch
好
OK
说出来
Say it
没有东西
There isn't anything--
根本没东西
Ain't nothing--
根本没东西能又大又凶
Ain't nothing too big or too ornery
到你抓不住的地步
for you to catch
可是
But--
But
而且
And
我们
We
会死
Die
没错  但是
Yeah but
你看
You see
不
No
死掉
Die
虫来过的迹象
Worm sign
牌 子
虫子
它就在这洞里
He's in that cave
珊迪  你确定你
Sandy are you sure you--
那当然了
Of course I am
我要进去了
I'm going in
不做一大盘炖虫子我绝不出来
And I ain't coming out
until I got me a big heaping plate of worm stew
找到你了  偷尾巴的害虫
There you are you tail nabbing varmit
我快赢了  海绵宝宝
I'm winning Spongebob
珊迪  那不是
Sandy, that's not--
应该不会太久的
This shouldn't take long
珊迪  那不是
Sandy, that's not--
快好了
Almost done
珊迪
Sandy
抓到它了  海绵宝宝
I got him, Spongebob
珊迪
Sandy?
好家伙
Boy howdy
这东西还挺不好打
This critter put up some sort of fight
但我可是德克萨斯来的
But I'm from Texas
你也能看得出来  没有虫子是我对手
And as you can see, no worm is a match for me
我连我尾巴都找到了
I even found my tail
那不是虫子
That's not the worm
说什么
Pardon?
那不是虫子
That not the worm
是虫子的舌头
That's his tongue
这个是舌头
This is the tongue
这一整个才是虫子
and the whole thing is the worm--
快逃命啊
Run for your life
有什么计划  珊迪
So what the plan, Sandy?
跑快点
Run faster
我本来能想到的
I could have thought of that
先等一下
Wait a minute
我说的对吧
I was right, wasn't I?
等会再说
Later
它太大  你抓不了吧
He is too big for you, isn't he?
现在不是时候  海绵宝宝
Not now Spongebob
我要听你说出来
I want to hear you say it
能不能以后再说这件事
Can we talk about this some other time?
说出来
Say it
海绵宝宝
Spongebob
不说我就绊倒你
Say it or I'll trip you
别
No
别瞎说
Get away
说出来
Say it
还不是时候
Not now
说出来
Say it
好
OK
你一直都对  我一直都错
You were right and I was wrong
我一直错错错错
I was wrong, wrong wrong, wrong
这下高兴了吧
Are you happy now?
我就知道
I knew it
又来了
Not again
珊迪
Sandy?
怎么了
Yeah?
现在该怎么办
What do we do now?
有了
I've got it
海绵宝宝  你还有回形针跟线头吗
Spongebob, you still got
that paperclip and that string?
我早想到了  珊迪
I'm way ahead of you Sandy
你看
Look
这是个项链
It's a necklace
S表示海绵宝宝  也可以表示珊迪
S for Spongebob, or S for Sandy
这样我们遗体身份就清楚了
That way they can identify our bodies
不对  笨蛋
No silly
让这个S表示保命如何
How about S for save our skins?
这样才叫牛仔表演
Now this is what I call a rodeo
待在上面就能平安无事了
We'll be nice and safe up here
我们成功了
We did it
这下它出不来了
He'll never get out of there
我们拯救了裤头村
We saved the town
去跟大家报喜吧
Let's go tell everybody
推
Push